<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CadAppForUser</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="text_with_paragraphs">
        Flexibility means that customers receive full refund in case of cancellation no later than 2 hours before booked time.
        Moderate means that customers get full refund if canceled no later than 1 day before booked time .
        Strictly  means that  customers get  full refund if canceled no later than 2 days  before booked time.

    </string>


    <string name="text_with_paragraphs1">
       Instant booking means that customers can book you directly within your availability period without their booking request being reviewed
        and approved by you first.
    </string>

    <string name="search">
        Search by services,companies,name
    </string>


    <string name="aboutus">
Creators desire solutions is one of the top system integrator partners offering an entire range of IT
integrated products and services. Incorporated in the year 2017 and has emerged as one of the
 fastest growing IT Infrastructure Solution provider supporting customers from small and medium
 businesses to blue chip clients and also providing a specialist service for the educational institute.
 CDS has extensive experience in delivering high-quality
IT services for all kinds of verticals and
 technology environments. Driven by a customer
 oriented approach with focus on absolute standards
of operational excellence, each experience has made us
 develop more innovative solutions provider, and has
enabled us to understand business, technology and operational
 elements in great detail. We want to empower
our customers to be able to reach their goals easily
and live a more fulfilling and productive life. .    </string>


    <string name="services">
       first male services then female then category then sub category
    </string>


    <string name="signup">
     Dont have an account?</string>

    <string name="profile_desc">Rowan Sebastian Atkinson CBE is an English actor,  comedian and screenwriter</string>
    <string name="profile_title">Mr Bean</string>
    <string name="posts">posts</string>
    <string name="followers">followers</string>
    <string name="following">following</string>
    <string name="msg_error_unable_select_profile_pic">Unable to set profile image. Please try again!</string>
    <string name="lbl_set_profile_photo">Set profile image</string>
    <string name="lbl_take_camera_picture">Take a picture</string>
    <string name="lbl_choose_from_gallery">Choose from gallery</string>
    <string name="toast_image_intent_null">Image picker option is missing!</string>


    <string name="terms">
       I have read and agree to V4U India Terms and Conditions and Private Policy.

    </string>

    <string name="condition">
        I wish  V4U India to deduct taxes and pay social security
        contributation  to me for the income I recieve for my assignmnets . which means I get payment as a net salary (the next salary will be about half
        of the price you specify ). I am self- employed via V4U India. which means that i will also be insured .I accepet terms and conditions and self
        - employment agreements
    </string>


    <string-array name="team">

        <item>Team Size[1 to 10]</item>
        <item>Team Size[10 to 20]</item>
        <item>Team Size[20 to 30]</item>
        <item>Team Size[30 to 40]</item>
        <item>Team Size[40 to 50]</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="male">

        <item>5</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>25</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="female">

        <item>5</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>25</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>

